Guide to the Firebrand Books records, 1984-2000.
Firebrand Books records,
- Series I. Author/Book Files
  - Too Queer: General, 1998-2000 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Too Queer: General, 1994-1997 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Too Queer: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Too Queer: Essays from a Radical Life by Victoria A. Brownworth, Firebrand Books 1996 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Too Queer: Reviews, 1996-1998 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - Too Queer: Review Copies, 1996-1999 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - Trash: Pending, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - Trash: Contracts, 1986-2000 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - Trash: Contracts, 1991-1998 (Box 28, Folder 16)
  - Trash: (British Editions) by Dorothy Allison, Flamingo 1988, 1991, 1995 Penguin Books 1988, 1990, 1990-1995 (Box 28, Folder 17)
  - Trash: General, 2000-2001 (Box 28, Folder 18)
  - Trash: General, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 19)
  - Trash: General, 1996-1997 (Box 28, Folder 20)
  - Trash: General, 1994-1995 (Box 28, Folder 21)
  - Trash: General, 1992-1993 (Box 28, Folder 22)
  - Trash: General, 1989-1991 (Box 28, Folder 23)
  - Trash: General, 1983-1999 (Box 28, Folder 24)
  - Trash: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 28, Folder 25)
  - Trash: Stories by Dorothy Allison, Firebrand Books 1988 (Box 28, Folder 26)
  - Trash: Reviews, 1988-1996 (Box 28, Folder 27)
  - Trash: Review Copies, 1988-1999 (Box 28, Folder 28)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: Pending, 1995-1999 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: Contracts, 1993-2000 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Wilde Lesbenwelt: (Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For-German Edition) by Alison Bechdel, Daphne 1995, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1996-1998 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: General, 1993-1995 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: Reviews, 1995-1997 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Unnatural Dykes to Watch Out For: Review Copies, 1995-2000 (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Pending, 1997 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Waiting In the Wings: General, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Waiting In the Wings: General, 1997-1998 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - Waiting In the Wings: General, 1996 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Portrait of a Queer Motherhood by Cherrie Moraga, Firebrand Books 1997 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Reviews, 1997-1999 (Box 29, Folder 17)
  - Waiting In the Wings: Review Copies, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 18)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Pending, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 19)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Contracts, 1992-2000 (Box 29, Folder 20)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: by Minnie Bruce Pratt, Spinsters/Aunt Lute 1985 (Box 29, Folder 21)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: General, 1996-2000 (Box 29, Folder 22)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: General, 1992-1995 (Box 29, Folder 23)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 24)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Poetry by Minnie Bruce Pratt, Firebrand Books 1985, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Reviews, 1992-1994 (Box 29, Folder 26)
  - We Say We Love Each Other: Review Copies, 1992-1999 (Box 29, Folder 27)
  - The Wolf Ticket: Pending, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 28)
  - The Wolf Ticket: Contracts, 1997-2000 (Box 29, Folder 29)
  - The Wolf Ticket: General, 1998-2000 (Box 29, Folder 30)
  - The Wolf Ticket: General, 1996-1997 (Box 29, Folder 31)
  - The Wolf Ticket: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 32)
  - The Wolf Ticket: A Novel by Caro Clarke, Firebrand Books 1998 (Box 29, Folder 33)
  - Le Llei del Llop: (The Wolf Ticket, Basque edition. Barcelona: Llibres de l'Index); and, La Ley del Lobo: (The Wolf Ticket, Spanish edition. Barcelona: Ediciones de la Tempestad, Llibres de l'Index); 2001 (Box 29, Folder 34)
  - The Wolf Ticket: Reviews, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 35)
  - The Wolf Ticket: Review Copies, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 36)
  - Women on the Row: Pending, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 37)
  - Women on the Row: Contracts, 1996-2000 (Box 29, Folder 38)
  - Women and the Death Penalty In the United States 1990-1998: by Kathleen O'Shea, Praeger Publishers 1999 (Box 29, Folder 39)
  - Women on the Row: General, 2000 (Box 29, Folder 40)
  - Women on the Row: General, 1999-2000 (Box 29, Folder 41)
  - Women on the Row: General, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 42)
  - Women on the Row: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 29, Folder 43)
  - Women on the Row: Revelations from Both Sides of the Bars by Kathleen O'Shea, Firebrand Books 2000 (Box 29, Folder 44)
  - Women on the Row: Reviews, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Women on the Row: Review Copies, 2000 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Pending, 1990-1997 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Contracts, 1990-2000 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: tape cassette "Sound Circle performing 'Butter My Tongue'", 2000; tr-11678 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: General, 1998-2000 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: General, 1994-1997 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: General, 1985-1993 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Poetry 1980-1990 by Dorothy Allison, Firebrand Books 1991 (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Reviews, 1983-1996 (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - The Women Who Hate Me: Review Copies, 1989-1999 (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Words to the Wise: General, 1990-1999 (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Words to the Wise: General, 1985-1989 (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Words to the Wise: A Writer's Guide to Feminist and Lesbian Periodical & Publishers by Andrea Fleck Clardy, Firebrand Books 1986, 1987, 1990, 1993 and Promo Materials, 1986-1993 (Box 30, Folder 15)
  - Words to the Wise: Reviews, 1986-1996 (Box 30, Folder 16)
  - Words to the Wise: Review Copies, 1990-1999 (Box 30, Folder 17)
  - Words to the Wise: Review Copies, 1986-1990 (Box 30, Folder 18)
  - Words to the Wise: Original Ms. Version, 1985 (Box 30, Folder 19)
  - Words to the Wise: Manuscript, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 20)
  - Words to the Wise: Publishing Notes, Clippings, etc., 1984-1986 (Box 30, Folder 21)
  - Words to the Wise: Publishers Lists, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 22)
  - Words to the Wise: Resources, 1985-1986 (Box 30, Folder 23)
  - Words to the Wise: Correspondence with Various Publishers, 1984-1993 (Box 30, Folder 24)
  - Words to the Wise: Feminist Presses-lists and articles (Box 30, Folder 25)
  - Words to the Wise: University Presses, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 26)
  - Words to the Wise: Miscellaneous Notes, Address Lists, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 27)
  - Words to the Wise: Design, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 28)
  - Words to the Wise: Jinx Beers and The Lesbian News, 1987 (Box 30, Folder 29)
  - Words to the Wise: "Not Yet Dealt With", 1985 (Box 30, Folder 30)
  - Words to the Wise: "Not Included- R.R.R., Bergin and Garvey, Lace, 10 Speed, Al[l]yson (sic.), St. Martin", 1984-1985 (Box 30, Folder 31)
  - Words to the Wise: Correspondence with Firebrand, 1987-1992 (Box 30, Folder 32)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaires & Cover Letters, 1986-1990 (Box 30, Folder 33)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaire- Periodicals A-K, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 34)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaire- Periodicals L-R, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 35)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaire- Periodicals S-Z, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 36)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaire- Publishers A-K, n.d. (Box 30, Folder 37)
  - Words to the Wise: Questionnaire- Publishers L-Z, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Words to the Wise: Manuscript, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Words to the Wise: 2nd edition New Entries, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Words to the Wise: 2nd edition Revisions, 1987 (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition Revisions, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition Revisions, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition Revisions, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition New Entries, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition New Entries, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Words to the Wise: 3rd edition Manuscript, 1990 (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Words to the Wise: 4th edition Presses, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Words to the Wise: 4th edition Resources, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 12)
  - Words to the Wise: 4th edition Periodicals, n.d. (Box 31, Folder 13)
  - Words to the Wise: Returned Mail-requests for entry revisions, 1985-1990 (Box 31, Folder 14)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Lupe Anguiano (Box 31, Folder 15)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: PEWS and Peter Lazes (Box 31, Folder 16)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Citizen's Network Advisory Board (Box 31, Folder 17)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 18)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Ithaca Festival Resource Committee (Box 31, Folder 19)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Dusty Was My Friend (Box 31, Folder 20)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Personal Correspondence (Box 31, Folder 21)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Clippings from Jean B. Hall (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Warren Clardy Clippings (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Personal Files (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Andrea Fleck Clardy: Women's History Research (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - The Worry Girl: Pending, 1992 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - The Worry Girl: Contracts, 1991-2000 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - The Worry Girl: Stories From a Childhood (British Edition) by Andrea Freud Loewenstein, The Women's Press 1992, 1993 and Das Sorgenmadchen: (The Worry Girl-German Edition) by Andrea Freud Loewenstein, ECON 1992, 1994, 1993-1994 (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - The Worry Girl: General, 1993-2000 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - The Worry Girl: General, 1990-1992 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - The Worry Girl: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - The Worry Girl: Stories From a Childhood by Andrea Freud Loewenstein, Firebrand Books 1992 (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - The Worry Girl: Reviews, 1991-1996 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - The Worry Girl: Review Copies, 1992-1999 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Yours In Struggle: Pending, 1988-1996 (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Yours In Struggle: Contracts, 1985-2000 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1999-2001 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1997-1998 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1995-1996 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1994 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1992-1993 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1989-1991 (Box 32, Folder 21)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1987-1988 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Yours In Struggle: General, 1985-1986 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Yours In Struggle: Promo Materials, n.d. (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Yours In Struggle: Three Feminist Perspectives on Anti-Semitism and Racism by Elly Bulkin, Minnie Bruce Pratt, and Barbara Smith, Firebrand Books 1984 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Yours In Struggle: Reviews, 1984-1999 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Yours In Struggle: Review Copies, 1986-2000 (Box 32, Folder 27)
- Manuscript Rejections
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1984-1985 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1987 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1991 (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1992 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1993 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 38, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1998 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 15)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 16)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 17)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 18)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 19)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 20)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 21)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 22)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 42, Folder 23)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Manuscript Rejections, 2000 (Box 43, Folder 7)
- Series III. Financial Records
  - Invoices #101-#1028, Apr. 1985-June 1985 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #1029-#1105, July 1985-Sept. 1985 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #1106-#1159, Sept. 1985-Oct. 1985 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Invoices #1160-#1219, Oct. 1985-Dec. 1985 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Invoices #1220-#1269, Dec. 1985-Jan. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Invoices #1270-#1309, Jan. 1986-Mar. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Invoices #1310-#1359, Feb. 1986-Mar. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Invoices #1360-#1409, Mar. 1986-Apr. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Invoices #1410-#1459, Apr. 1986-May 1986 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Invoices #1460-#1500L, May 1986-June 1986 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Invoices #1500M-#1509, June 1986-July 1986 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Invoices #1510-#1559, July 1986-Aug. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - Invoices #1560-#1609, Aug. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - Invoices #1610-#1659, Aug. 1986-Sept. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - Invoices #1660-#1709, Sept. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - Invoices #1710-#1759, Sept. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - Invoices #1760-#1809, Sept. 1986-Oct. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - Invoices #1810-#1859, Oct. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Invoices #1860-#1909, Oct. 1986-Nov. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Invoices #1910-#1959, Nov. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Invoices #1960-#2009, Nov. 1986-Dec. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Invoices #2010-#2059, Dec. 1986 (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Invoices #2060-#2109, Dec. 1986-Jan. 1987 (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Invoices #2110-#2159, Jan. 1987-Feb. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Invoices #2160-#2209, Feb. 1987-Mar. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Invoices #2210-#2259, Mar. 1987 (Box 45, Folder 3)